{
    "subject": "resource/Maria_Letizia_Bonaparte,_Duchess_of_Aosta",
    "predicate": "property/house",
    "object": "resource/House_of_Bonaparte",
    "human_readable": "Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta's house is the House of Bonaparte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9669418334960938,
            "question": "What is the name of the house associated with Maria Letizia Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806219100952148,
            "question": "Who was Maria Letizia Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733099102973938,
            "question": "Can you name other prominent members of the House of Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7168855667114258,
            "question": "What title did Maria Letizia Bonaparte hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.682279646396637,
            "question": "What was the historical significance of the House of Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.681989312171936,
            "question": "To which royal family does Maria Letizia Bonaparte belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6780235171318054,
            "question": "Are there any famous individuals related to the House of Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593382358551025,
            "question": "Were there any significant events associated with the House of Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6587316989898682,
            "question": "What can you tell about the House of Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4768347144126892,
            "question": "How did Maria Letizia Bonaparte contribute to her family's legacy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta's house is the House of Bonaparte.",
            "html": "dbpedia_972_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell about the House of Bonaparte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_972_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant events associated with the House of Bonaparte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_972_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous individuals related to the House of Bonaparte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_972_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_972_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Maria Letizia Bonaparte was one of three children born to Prince Napol\u00e9on and his wife Princess Maria Clotilde of Savoy, and that she married Prince Amadeo, Duke of Aosta. However, they do not provide any information about her house being the House of Bonaparte, but rather mention that \"Their marriage was instrumental in almost reviving French hopes of reinstating the Bonaparte dynasty into a position of power...\" which suggests that she is related to the Bonaparte family, but does not confirm whether she was part of the House of Bonaparte herself."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta, including her lineage and connections to the Bonaparte family. While direct statements about \"House of Bonaparte\" are not explicitly mentioned in the provided context, the connection to the Bonapartes as a noble family and her title suggest that she is associated with the House of Bonaparte, supporting the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta was married to Prince Amadeo, Duke of Aosta, a member of the House of Savoy, not the House of Bonaparte.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}